// Making an array of questions

let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What are the 4 strokes of a 4 stroke engine?",
        answer: "intake, compression, combustion and exhaust",
        options: [
            "intake, compression, combustion and exhaust",
            "injection, rotation, combustion ehaust",
            "injection, carburetion, rotation and exhaust",
            "up, down, left, right"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "A crankshafts job in an engine is to?",
        answer: "change linear motion into rotational motion",
        options: [
            "deliver fuel to the cylinders",
            "keep cylinder heads in place",
            "crank start the engine",
            "change linear motion into rotational motion"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What are the 2 main components of an engines cooling system?",
        answer: "radiator and water pump",
        options: [
            "battery and fan",
            "radiator and water pump",
            "air intake and turbocharger",
            "blower motor and condenser"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What are 3 common ways to deliver fuel to an engine?",
        answer: "carburetion, port fuel injection, direct fuel injection",
        options: [
            "carburetion, hybridization, electrical charging",
            "carburetion, port fuel injection, direct fuel injection",
            "fuel injection, infusion, circulation",
            "pump, gravity, funnel and a fuel can"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What are the 3 functions of engine oil?",
        answer: "lubrication, cooling, cleaning",
        options: [
            "lubrication, making fuel powerful, expell exhaust smell",
            "cooling, cleaning, making money for Jiffylube",
            "lubrication, cooling, cleaning",
            "get dirty, make a mess, spend money "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Ohm's law does not apply to?",
        answer: "semi-conductors",
        options: [
            "semi-conductors",
            "small resistors",
            "AC currents",
            "DC currents"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is the unit of electrical potential?",
        answer: "Volts",
        options: [
            "Ampere",
            "Volts",
            "Volt-ampere",
            "Ohms"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What unit is used to measure resistance?",
        answer: "Ohms",
        options: [
            "Volts",
            "Ohms",
            "Amperes",
            "Tesla"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "How man cycles does a sine wave go through in 10s at 60hz?",
        answer: "600 cycles",
        options: [
            "10 cycles",
            "60 cycles",
            "120 cycles",
            "600 cycles"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What is the safest current value the human body can carry for 3 seconds?",
        answer: "9 ma",
        options: [
            "4 ma",
            "9 ma",
            "15 ma",
            "25 ma"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "Single acting cylinders can be pressurized:",
        answer: "from one direction",
        options: [
            "only once",
            "from one direction",
            "from both directions",
            "once after being reset"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "Hydraulic systems use __ to transfer force?",
        answer: "Liquid",
        options: [
            "Air",
            "Solid",
            "Liquid",
            "Gas"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "Liquids transmit __ in all directions?",
        answer: "Applied pressure or force",
        options: [
            "Shape",
            "Work force",
            "Applied pressure or force",
            "Light"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "Which of these generates rotary movement using hydraulic power?",
        answer: "Hydraulic Motor",
        options: [
            "Hydraulic Pump",
            "Hydraulic Motor",
            "Pressure Relief Valve",
            "Cylinder"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "What allows flow in one direction only?",
        answer: "Check Valve",
        options: [
            "Flow Control Valve",
            "Shut Off Valve",
            "Pressure Relief Valve",
            "Check Valve"
        ]
    },
]